[{"answer": "Well, they can interview him as many times as he is willing to do so.", "docId": "130423pmt", "aSentId": 34, "question": "How long can they continue to interrogate him for?", "qSentId": 33}, {"answer": "Right, and this denial is led by their mother, Zubeidat Tsarnaev, who gave this extraordinary interview to CNN.", "docId": "130423pmt", "aSentId": 75, "question": "They say how could these good Muslims do this, kill innocent people, Piers?", "qSentId": 74}, {"answer": "The youngest one, I would say probably two years for the first two years.", "docId": "130423pmt", "aSentId": 109, "question": "And the younger one?", "qSentId": 108}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "130423pmt", "aSentId": 112, "question": "Is that correct?", "qSentId": 111}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "130423pmt", "aSentId": 119, "question": "Did he explain why he needed it?", "qSentId": 118}, {"answer": "On Tuesday was the first time that I see him acting the way he was acting.", "docId": "130423pmt", "aSentId": 125, "question": "He would you describe his behavior?", "qSentId": 124}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "130423pmt", "aSentId": 131, "question": "Did he pay you for the repair works to the car?", "qSentId": 130}, {"answer": "He's always quiet.", "docId": "130423pmt", "aSentId": 139, "question": "How would you describe him?", "qSentId": 138}, {"answer": "Very kind.", "docId": "130423pmt", "aSentId": 169, "question": "How would you describe him?", "qSentId": 168}, {"answer": "I saw him two weeks before the incident and he was exactly the same Dzhokhar as always.", "docId": "130423pmt", "aSentId": 175, "question": "Did anything in his behavioral pattern in the last few months say to you something is not quite right here?", "qSentId": 174}, {"answer": "I mean, it's really hard to think about it just because you never think that one of your friends can just become a terrorist any time.", "docId": "130423pmt", "aSentId": 180, "question": "Can you believe that he is capable of doing what he has alleged to have done?", "qSentId": 179}, {"answer": "I know he followed Islamic stuff on Twitter.", "docId": "130423pmt", "aSentId": 187, "question": "A political nature?", "qSentId": 186}, {"answer": "Two of my friends saw him at the gym the day after the bombing at like 9:00 or 10:00 at night, they said.", "docId": "130423pmt", "aSentId": 192, "question": "What did he say about his demeanor?", "qSentId": 191}, {"answer": "Not true.", "docId": "130423pmt", "aSentId": 233, "question": "Not true?", "qSentId": 232}, {"answer": "ENNEBERRY: No, no.", "docId": "130423pmt", "aSentId": 240, "question": "No?", "qSentId": 239}, {"answer": "A good amount of blood.", "docId": "130423pmt", "aSentId": 247, "question": "A lot of blood?", "qSentId": 246}, {"answer": "Oh my God.", "docId": "130423pmt", "aSentId": 254, "question": "What were you thinking at that moment?", "qSentId": 253}, {"answer": "You can't!", "docId": "130423pmt", "aSentId": 287, "question": "I mean, you couldn't make that up, could you?", "qSentId": 286}, {"answer": "It was probably one of the most amazing spiritual moments of my life, Piers.", "docId": "130423pmt", "aSentId": 302, "question": "What was the moment like for you?", "qSentId": 301}, {"answer": "We met.", "docId": "130423pmt", "aSentId": 304, "question": "You walked in to see her at the hospital and what happened?", "qSentId": 303}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "130423pmt", "aSentId": 319, "question": "Did she thank you?", "qSentId": 318}, {"answer": "OBB: She seems to be doing really well.", "docId": "130423pmt", "aSentId": 329, "question": "How is she doing?", "qSentId": 328}, {"answer": "(on the phone): I'm overwhelmed.", "docId": "130423pmt", "aSentId": 360, "question": "How do you feel about this?", "qSentId": 359}, {"answer": "You just said it.", "docId": "130423pmt", "aSentId": 371, "question": "What were you think?", "qSentId": 370}, {"answer": "I do now.", "docId": "130423pmt", "aSentId": 396, "question": "Do you have a suspicion as to who has done this to you?", "qSentId": 395}, {"answer": "Well, you know, I am an entertainer.", "docId": "130423pmt", "aSentId": 411, "question": "The person you believe did this to you, why would they do that to you?", "qSentId": 410}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "130423pmt", "aSentId": 419, "question": "But Kevin, this particular guy that you -- I think it's a man that you suspect, have you had an ongoing feud with him?", "qSentId": 418}, {"answer": "I have.", "docId": "130423pmt", "aSentId": 438, "question": "Have you met this person?", "qSentId": 437}, {"answer": "Oh, no.", "docId": "130423pmt", "aSentId": 443, "question": "Was it a hostile encounter?", "qSentId": 442}, {"answer": "To my understanding, he already is and his home is quarantined by the federal agent.", "docId": "130423pmt", "aSentId": 459, "question": "Have they led you to believe that will happen?", "qSentId": 458}, {"answer": "I'm going to be on \"Good Morning America\" in the morning.", "docId": "130423pmt", "aSentId": 464, "question": "Are you performing?", "qSentId": 463}, {"answer": "Oh, absolutely.", "docId": "130423pmt", "aSentId": 514, "question": "But if she is, the FBI, who she is talking about there, is being in repeated contract with both Tamerlan Tsarnaev and with her, have questions to answer, don't they?", "qSentId": 513}, {"answer": "Well, civil libertarians are very concerned about surveiling every suspicious person.", "docId": "130423pmt", "aSentId": 532, "question": "What could they have done legally?", "qSentId": 531}, {"answer": "No, absolutely not.", "docId": "130423pmt", "aSentId": 570, "question": "To me, this all stinks to high heaven of some other entity being involved, because they couldn't have just learned all this stuff, could they, from the Internet?", "qSentId": 569}, {"answer": "Well, I believe that there's enough information that has come to light since the bombings that will cause investigators to take another really close, hard look at this.", "docId": "130423pmt", "aSentId": 596, "question": "But the bottom line is this: do you believe there is any link between Tamerlan Tsarnaev and this triple killing involving one of his best friends?", "qSentId": 595}, {"answer": "Well, I think the belief at the time was that this was probably a drug-related murder.", "docId": "130423pmt", "aSentId": 601, "question": "And what was the belief at the time in terms of who had done it?", "qSentId": 600}, {"answer": "Well, I was stopped about eight blocks from the finish line.", "docId": "130423pmt", "aSentId": 618, "question": "What are your memories of that day, given the appalling events that happened?", "qSentId": 617}]